If you want to track conversions,
如果你想对转化进行跟踪
you need to tell Google Analytics what your goals are.
你需要告诉 Google Analytics 你的目标是什么
You do that in the admin section of your Google Analytics account.
你可以在 Google Analytics 帐户的管理部分中执行此操作
Here, Google let's you specify your goals.
在这里 Google 会让你指定你的目标
Let's walk through one example of setting up a goal.
我们来看一个设定目标的例子
Of course, since there are different types of goals,
当然 由于有不同类型的目标
the set up will differ from goal to goal,
目标设定也会有所不同
but this will help you to understand the underlying process.
但是这会帮助你理解潜在的过程
If you want to learn more about this,
如果你想了解更多这方面的信息
you can do so in a link that I've added in the notes below.
你可以在我在下面的笔记添加的链接中进行此操作
I'm going to walk through the set up of a goal for the Udacity website.
我来为优达学城网站设定一个目标
As you may know, Udacity runs a nanodegree for self-driving car engineering.
正如你可能知道的那样 优达学城为无人驾驶汽车工程设置了一个纳米学位
For this degree, interested students need to apply.
对于这个学位 有兴趣的学员需要进行申请
It is our goal to get as many applications as possible,
我们的目标是获得尽可能多的申请
thus an application for this program is an important conversion for us.
因此对这门课程的申请对我们来说就是一个重要的转化
Let me show you how students might convert.
我来向你示范一下学员是如何转化的
They land on our home page, here,
他们在这里登陆我们的主页
and they may go into exploring our nanodegree programs.
他们可能会去探索我们的纳米学位课程
Here, they can find the self-driving car engineering nanodegree.
在这里 他们可以找到无人驾驶汽车工程纳米学位
Then may click on that.
然后可以点击它
And once they're here,
一旦他们来到这里
they find a little bit more information and may decide to apply now.
他们就会发现更多的信息 并可能决定现在就申请
They then have to fill out the application form and hit the submit button,
然后他们必须填写申请表并点击
which is here at the bottom.
底部的提交按钮
Then, they get this lovely page telling them their application was submitted.
然后 他们得到了这个可爱的页面告诉他们 他们的申请已经提交
If I track how many people got to see this page,
如果我跟踪一下有多少人看到这个网页
then I will know how many people converted and applied.
那么我会知道有多少人进行了转化和申请
So, I can set this up as a destination goal in Google Analytics.
所以 我可以在 Google Analytics 中将其设置为终点目标
And my destination is this exact page. With this URL.
而我的终点正是这个网页  利用这个 URL
Let's see how that process works.
让我们看看这个过程是如何进行的
Goals are defined at the "View" level.
在“查看”级别定义目标
I'm here in the "All User Level" for the Udacity account.
我现在在优达学城账户的“所有用户级别”处
This is a view I've set up for walk-throughs like this one.
这是我为此次演示设置的一个视图
I am in the "Admin" section here where I can select "Goals".
我现在在“管理”部分 在这里我可以选择“目标”
So let's set up a new goal.
那么我们来设立一个新的目标
There are three big chunks in the process of setting up a goal.
在制定目标的过程中有三大块
There is the general goal set up,
有一个总目标需要建立起来
then there is the goal description and there are the goal details.
然后是目标描述和目标细节
In the goal set up, I have the option to select a preset template,
在目标设定中 我有一个可以选择预设模板的选项
or I can use a custom setup.
或者我可以使用自定义设置
There happens to be a template here that exactly describes my goal, submission.
这里恰好有一个模板 正好描述了我的目标 提交
You see it's a template I can use for the submission of an application,
你看它就是我可以用来提交申请的模板
so I'm going to select that.
所以我要选择它
Then, I get to describe my goal.
然后 我来描述我的目标
I can give it a name so I will recognize later what this goal was all about.
我可以给它一个名字 这样以后我会认出这个目标是关于什么的
Let's call this one "Submission for the carND".
我们把这称为“carND的提交”
The goal gets assigned a number.
这个目标被分配了一个数字
This is my second goal,
这是我的第二个目标
so this seems fine.
这样看起来似乎很不错
Then I can choose the goal type.
然后我可以选择目标类型
As we said this is a destination goal,
正如我们所说的 这是一个终点目标
because I ultimately want to monitor
因为我最终想要监控
how many people made it to my "Application Submitted" page.
有多少人到了我的“申请提交”页面
So, destination here is correct.
所以 这里的终点是正确的
Let me go to the next step then, the "Goal details".
然后我继续下一步 “目标细节”
Since this is destination goal,
由于这是终点目标
we have to tell Google Analytics what the destination is.
所以我们必须告诉 Google Analytics 终点是哪里
In our case, the destination equals the following URL.
在我们的案例中 终点等于下面的 URL
Note how I can drop the first part the URL, here.
请注意 看我怎样在这里丢掉 URL 的第一部分
Google will still recognize it.
Google 会仍然认识它
Then we can assign a value to this URL.
然后我们可以给这个 URL 分配一个值
Well, hypothetically, let's say that ten percent of
好了 我们假设有百分之十的
the people that apply actually get started with the degree,
申请人真正开始了学位的学习
and that the associated price is $800.
而相关的价格是 800 美元
Then, each application is worth eighty to us.
那么 每个申请对我们来说都值八十
Let's use that for the value.
我们用它来表示这个值
We can also describe the expected path that
我们也可以描述
we believe users will take to get to this goal.
我们相信用户为实现这一目标而采取的预期路径
That's called a funnel.
这就是所谓的漏斗
You don't have to do that,
你不是一定得这么做
but if you have a typical path that leads to this goal,
但是如果你有一条通向这个目标的典型路径
it can be interesting to tell Google Analytics what that path is.
那么把这个路径告诉 Google Analytics 会非常有趣
Then, Google Analytics can show you in
这样 Google Analytics 可以在报告中向你显示
the reports where users get stuck in the path and leave.
用户在路径中停留并离开的信息
So, let's put in the typical path that we walked through.
所以 让我们把我们演示的路径设为典型路径
So, in order to get through the application process,
这样 为了通过申请程序
I'm assuming that most of my students are starting at
我假设我的大部分学员都是从
a nanodegree overview page. So, let's type that in.
纳米学位概述页面开始的 因此我们把它键入进去
This is the associated URL.
这就是关联的 URL
And remember, I don't need that first part of the URL.
请记住 我不需要 URL 的第一部分
Then Google asks me whether this page is required.
然后 Google 问我是否需要这个页面
And in this case, it's not really required to get on to the next step.
在这种情况下 其实并不需要进行下一步
So, I'm going to leave this as "No".
所以 我会把这个写成“不”
Next stop is the carND page, and its URL.
下一站是 carND 页面和它的 URL
And I remember this one was "drive".
我记得这个是“驾驶”
Then the user comes to the application page and the associated URL.
然后 用户来到申请页面和关联的 URL
This one is a little bit more complex.
这个比较复杂一点
And again, we don't need the first part.
然后再重复一次 我们不需要第一部分
After this page, the user reaches the goal destination,
在这个页面之后 用户到达目标终点
the applications submitted page.
申请提交页面
But that one we don't need to make part of the funnel
但是 我们不需要把那个做成漏斗的一部分
as it is already considered as the end destination.
因为它已被视为最终目的地
So, now my goal is set up and I can save it.
所以 现在我的目标已经建立 我可以保存它
I will then be able to track this conversion in my Google Analytics reports.
然后 我将能够在我的 Google Analytics 报告中跟踪此转化